Edly Mulya Andeslin

Fullstack Developer

I am a recent graduate with skills in web development, covering both front-end and back-end. I have worked on various projects that have honed my ability to create effective and user-friendly web applications. I am ready to start my career and contribute to a team. I am also committed to continuous learning and development.

Pekanbaru, Riau, Indonesia

edlymulyaandeslin@gmail.com | in f





Experience

IT Support • PT Garuda Cyber Indonesia (Internship)

September 2023 - December 2023 | Pekanbaru, Riau

- Development a project progress web application using the Laravel framework.
- Development a discussion forum web application using the Laravel framework.
- Development static web pages using template engines.
- Develop and implement routing features on websites using the Laravel framework.

Portfolio

July 2024 - July 2024 Shuttleslot Badminton Court API	Developing an API to digitize badminton court bookings to make it easier for court owners and customers. Using Golang language.
March 2024 - April 2024 Acne Diagnosis Expert System (SPDJ)	Spdj is a program created based on the knowledge of acne experts and implemented into the system, in order to help people who experience acne problems and provide treatment.
February 2024 - March 2024 E-Thesis Information System	E thesis is an application developed to assist students and information systems study programs in managing thesis academic activities in the delivery of information and making reports.
November 2023 - December 2023 Project progress application	The project progress application is an application developed to help companies manage internship students or intern employees.

Education



2020 - 2024

Pasir Pengaraian University

Information System



2017 - 2020

SMK Negeri 1 Rambah

Accountancy

Skills

HIGHLIGHT

- Laravel
- Livewire
- ReactJs
- NextJs
- Git
- MVC
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Gin Gonic

Programming Language

- PHP
- JavaScript
- Golang
- SQL

Language

- Indonesian Professional
- English

Powered by CakeResume